So you're looking for a new hair style.
Your hair may be short or fine.
And you want to sew in some hair extensions.
Well my name is Sylvia Russell, and this is how you sew in hair extensions.
So I have my hair, I've picked it curly and dark so that you can see the contrast between the light and the dark.
You can actually see how it's done.
You've got to first put a braid at the back of your hair.
This is the most conventional way to sew in hair extensions.
Once you've created your base of a braid, you can begin your hair extensions.
Now you're going to use a needle and thread like I have here.
And as you can see I've already attached it to the base hair extension that I'm going to use.
So now what I'm going to do is place it right on the braid, go under the braid, and through the top of the hair extension here.
Go ahead and use your thread to create a knot, pull your needle all the way through, and boom you first attached your hair.
So would simple create this all the way across the hair, remembering to take your time.
And remember, this is something that may be time consuming, so you'll want to make sure that you have plenty of time to finish.
It's something that is not the easiest to do yourself at home, you may want to check with your local professional who can give you a beautiful sew in hair extension.
My name is Sylvia Russell, and this is how you can sew in hair extensions.